[{"prompt": "Impuses are happy. Sterpus is impus. Sam is sterpus. True or false: Sam is happy. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Impuses are happy. Shumpus is numpus. Sam is sterpus. True or false: Sam is happy. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Sam is sterpus. Sterpus is impus. Sam is impus. Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_0": "Impuses are happy. Sam is happy.", "layer_1": "Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_2": "Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_3": "Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_4": "Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_5": "Sam is happy. True", "layer_6": "Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_7": "Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_8": "Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_9": "Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_10": "Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_11": "Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_12": "Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_13": "Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_14": "Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_15": "Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_16": "Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_17": "Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_18": "Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_19": "Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_20": "Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_21": "Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_22": "Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_23": "Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_24": "Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_25": "Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_26": "Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_27": "Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_28": "Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_29": "Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_30": "Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True", "layer_31": "Impuses are happy. Sam is happy. True"}, {"prompt": "Numpuses are discordant. Wumpuses are numpuses. Wren is wumpus. True or false: Wren is discordant. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Numpuses are discordant. Impus is rompus. Wren is wumpus. True or false: Wren is discordant. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Wren is wumpus. Wumpuses are numpuses. Wren is numpus. Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_0": "Wren is discordant. True.", "layer_1": "Numpuses are discordant. True", "layer_2": "Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_3": "Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_4": "Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_5": "Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_6": "Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_7": "Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_8": "Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_9": "Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_10": "Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_11": "Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_12": "Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_13": "Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_14": "Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_15": "Wren is discordant. True", "layer_16": "Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_17": "Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_18": "Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_19": "Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_20": "Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_21": "Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_22": "Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_23": "Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_24": "Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_25": "Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_26": "Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_27": "Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_28": "Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_29": "Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_30": "Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True", "layer_31": "Numpuses are discordant. Wren is discordant. True"}, {"prompt": "Tumpus is opaque. Yumpuses are tumpuses. Fae is yumpus. True or false: Fae is opaque. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Tumpus is opaque. Grimpus is lorpus. Fae is yumpus. True or false: Fae is opaque. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Fae is yumpus. Yumpuses are tumpuses. Fae is tumpus. Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_0": "Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_1": "Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_2": "Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_3": "Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_4": "Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_5": "Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_6": "Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_7": "Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_8": "Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_9": "Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_10": "Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_11": "Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_12": "Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_13": "Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_14": "Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_15": "Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_16": "Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_17": "Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_18": "Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_19": "Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_20": "Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_21": "Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_22": "Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_23": "Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_24": "Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_25": "Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_26": "Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_27": "Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_28": "Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_29": "Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_30": "Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True", "layer_31": "Tumpus is opaque. Fae is opaque. True"}, {"prompt": "Yumpuses are loud. Jompuses are yumpuses. Sam is jompus. True or false: Sam is loud. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Yumpuses are loud. Gorpus is impus. Sam is jompus. True or false: Sam is loud. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Sam is jompus. Jompuses are yumpuses. Sam is yumpus. Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_0": "Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True.", "layer_1": "Yumpuses are loud. True", "layer_2": "Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_3": "Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_4": "Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_5": "Yumpuses are loud. True", "layer_6": "Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_7": "Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_8": "Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_9": "Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_10": "Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_11": "Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_12": "Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_13": "Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_14": "Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_15": "Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_16": "Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_17": "Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_18": "Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_19": "Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_20": "Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_21": "Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_22": "Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_23": "Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_24": "Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_25": "Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_26": "Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_27": "Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_28": "Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_29": "Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_30": "Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True", "layer_31": "Yumpuses are loud. Sam is loud. True"}, {"prompt": "Yumpuses are spicy. Jompuses are yumpuses. Polly is jompus. True or false: Polly is spicy. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Yumpuses are spicy. Dumpus is grimpus. Polly is jompus. True or false: Polly is spicy. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Polly is jompus. Jompuses are yumpuses. Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_0": "Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_1": "Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_2": "Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_3": "Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_4": "Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_5": "Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_6": "Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_7": "Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_8": "Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_9": "Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_10": "Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_11": "Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_12": "Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_13": "Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_14": "Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_15": "Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_16": "Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_17": "Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_18": "Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_19": "Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_20": "Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_21": "Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_22": "Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_23": "Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_24": "Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_25": "Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_26": "Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_27": "Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_28": "Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_29": "Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_30": "Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True", "layer_31": "Yumpuses are spicy. Polly is spicy. True"}, {"prompt": "Jompus is wooden. Impus is jompus. Stella is impus. True or false: Stella is wooden. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Jompus is wooden. Gorpus is shumpus. Stella is impus. True or false: Stella is wooden. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Stella is impus. Impus is jompus. Stella is jompus. Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_0": "Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_1": "Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_2": "Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_3": "Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_4": "Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_5": "Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_6": "Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_7": "Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_8": "Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_9": "Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_10": "Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_11": "Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_12": "Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_13": "Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_14": "Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_15": "Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_16": "Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_17": "Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_18": "Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_19": "Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_20": "Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_21": "Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_22": "Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_23": "Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_24": "Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_25": "Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_26": "Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_27": "Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_28": "Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_29": "Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_30": "Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True", "layer_31": "Jompus is wooden. Stella is wooden. True"}, {"prompt": "Sterpuses are metallic. Dumpuses are sterpuses. Fae is dumpus. True or false: Fae is metallic. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Sterpuses are metallic. Tumpus is rompus. Fae is dumpus. True or false: Fae is metallic. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Fae is dumpus. Dumpuses are sterpuses. Fae is sterpus. Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_0": "Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True.", "layer_1": "Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_2": "Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_3": "Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_4": "Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_5": "Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_6": "Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_7": "Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_8": "Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_9": "Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_10": "Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_11": "Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_12": "Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_13": "Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_14": "Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_15": "Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_16": "Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_17": "Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_18": "Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_19": "Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_20": "Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_21": "Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_22": "Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_23": "Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_24": "Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_25": "Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_26": "Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_27": "Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_28": "Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_29": "Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_30": "Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True", "layer_31": "Sterpuses are metallic. Fae is metallic. True"}, {"prompt": "Impuses are cold. Jompuses are impuses. Fae is jompus. True or false: Fae is cold. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Impuses are cold. Sterpus is yumpus. Fae is jompus. True or false: Fae is cold. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Fae is jompus. Jompuses are impuses. Fae is impus. Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_0": "Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_1": "Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_2": "Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_3": "Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_4": "Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_5": "Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_6": "Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_7": "Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_8": "Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_9": "Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_10": "Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_11": "Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_12": "Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_13": "Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_14": "Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_15": "Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_16": "Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_17": "Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_18": "Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_19": "Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_20": "Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_21": "Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_22": "Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_23": "Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_24": "Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_25": "Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_26": "Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_27": "Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_28": "Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_29": "Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_30": "Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True", "layer_31": "Impuses are cold. Fae is cold. True"}, {"prompt": "Dumpuses are muffled. Impuses are dumpuses. Stella is impus. True or false: Stella is muffled. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Dumpuses are muffled. Vumpus is jompus. Stella is impus. True or false: Stella is muffled. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Stella is impus. Impuses are dumpuses. Stella is dumpus. Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True", "layer_0": "Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled.", "layer_1": "Stella is muffled. True", "layer_2": "Stella is muffled. True.", "layer_3": "Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True", "layer_4": "Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True", "layer_5": "Stella is muffled. False", "layer_6": "Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True", "layer_7": "Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True", "layer_8": "Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True", "layer_9": "Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True", "layer_10": "Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True", "layer_11": "Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True", "layer_12": "Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True", "layer_13": "Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True", "layer_14": "Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True", "layer_15": "Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True", "layer_16": "Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True", "layer_17": "Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True", "layer_18": "Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True", "layer_19": "Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True", "layer_20": "Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True", "layer_21": "Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True", "layer_22": "Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True", "layer_23": "Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True", "layer_24": "Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True", "layer_25": "Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True", "layer_26": "Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True", "layer_27": "Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True", "layer_28": "Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True", "layer_29": "Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True", "layer_30": "Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True", "layer_31": "Dumpuses are muffled. Stella is muffled. True"}, {"prompt": "Grimpuses are fruity. Lempuses are grimpuses. Alex is lempus. True or false: Alex is fruity. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Grimpuses are fruity. Gorpus is lorpus. Alex is lempus. True or false: Alex is fruity. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Alex is lempus. Lempuses are grimpuses. Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are fruity. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_0": "Alex is fruity. False", "layer_1": "Alex is fruity. True", "layer_2": "Grimpuses are fruity. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_3": "Grimpuses are fruity. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_4": "Grimpuses are fruity. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_5": "Alex is fruity. True", "layer_6": "Alex is fruity. True", "layer_7": "Grimpuses are fruity. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_8": "Grimpuses are fruity. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_9": "Grimpuses are fruity. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_10": "Alex is fruity. True", "layer_11": "Grimpuses are fruity. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_12": "Grimpuses are fruity. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_13": "Grimpuses are fruity. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_14": "Grimpuses are fruity. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_15": "Grimpuses are fruity. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_16": "Grimpuses are fruity. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_17": "Grimpuses are fruity. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_18": "Grimpuses are fruity. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_19": "Grimpuses are fruity. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_20": "Grimpuses are fruity. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_21": "Grimpuses are fruity. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_22": "Grimpuses are fruity. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_23": "Grimpuses are fruity. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_24": "Grimpuses are fruity. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_25": "Grimpuses are fruity. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_26": "Grimpuses are fruity. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_27": "Grimpuses are fruity. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_28": "Grimpuses are fruity. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_29": "Grimpuses are fruity. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_30": "Grimpuses are fruity. Alex is fruity. True", "layer_31": "Grimpuses are fruity. Alex is fruity. True"}, {"prompt": "Grimpuses are liquid. Gorpus is grimpus. Sam is gorpus. True or false: Sam is liquid. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Grimpuses are liquid. Lorpus is rompus. Sam is gorpus. True or false: Sam is liquid. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Sam is gorpus. Gorpus is grimpus. Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_0": "Impuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True ", "layer_1": "Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_2": "Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_3": "Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_4": "Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_5": "Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_6": "Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_7": "Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_8": "Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_9": "Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_10": "Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_11": "Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_12": "Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_13": "Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_14": "Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_15": "Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_16": "Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_17": "Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_18": "Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_19": "Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_20": "Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_21": "Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_22": "Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_23": "Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_24": "Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_25": "Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_26": "Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_27": "Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_28": "Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_29": "Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_30": "Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True", "layer_31": "Grimpuses are liquid. Sam is liquid. True"}, {"prompt": "Sterpuses are earthy. Impuses are sterpuses. Wren is impus. True or false: Wren is earthy. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Sterpuses are earthy. Vumpus is brimpus. Wren is impus. True or false: Wren is earthy. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Wren is impus. Impuses are sterpuses. Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_0": "Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy.", "layer_1": "Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_2": "Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_3": "Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_4": "Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_5": "Wren is earthy. True", "layer_6": "Sterpuses are earthy. True", "layer_7": "Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_8": "Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_9": "Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_10": "Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_11": "Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_12": "Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_13": "Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_14": "Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_15": "Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_16": "Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_17": "Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_18": "Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_19": "Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_20": "Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_21": "Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_22": "Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_23": "Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_24": "Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_25": "Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_26": "Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_27": "Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_28": "Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_29": "Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_30": "Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_31": "Sterpuses are earthy. Wren is earthy. True"}, {"prompt": "Tumpuses are opaque. Rompuses are tumpuses. Stella is rompus. True or false: Stella is opaque. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Tumpuses are opaque. Impus is dumpus. Stella is rompus. True or false: Stella is opaque. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Stella is rompus. Rompuses are tumpuses. Stella is tumpus. Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_0": "Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True.", "layer_1": "Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_2": "Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_3": "Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_4": "Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_5": "Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_6": "Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_7": "Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_8": "Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_9": "Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_10": "Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_11": "Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_12": "Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_13": "Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_14": "Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_15": "Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_16": "Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_17": "Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_18": "Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_19": "Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_20": "Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_21": "Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_22": "Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_23": "Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_24": "Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_25": "Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_26": "Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_27": "Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_28": "Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_29": "Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_30": "Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True", "layer_31": "Tumpuses are opaque. Stella is opaque. True"}, {"prompt": "Impuses are slow. Wumpuses are impuses. Sam is wumpus. True or false: Sam is slow. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Impuses are slow. Jompus is lempus. Sam is wumpus. True or false: Sam is slow. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Sam is wumpus. Wumpuses are impuses. Sam is impus. Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_0": "Sam is slow.", "layer_1": "Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_2": "Sam is slow. True", "layer_3": "Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_4": "Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_5": "Sam is slow. True", "layer_6": "Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_7": "Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_8": "Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_9": "Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_10": "Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_11": "Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_12": "Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_13": "Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_14": "Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_15": "Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_16": "Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_17": "Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_18": "Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_19": "Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_20": "Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_21": "Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_22": "Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_23": "Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_24": "Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_25": "Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_26": "Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_27": "Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_28": "Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_29": "Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_30": "Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True", "layer_31": "Impuses are slow. Sam is slow. True"}, {"prompt": "Sterpus is amenable. Yumpuses are sterpuses. Polly is yumpus. True or false: Polly is amenable. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Sterpus is amenable. Dumpus is lempus. Polly is yumpus. True or false: Polly is amenable. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Polly is yumpus. Yumpuses are sterpuses. Polly is sterpus. Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_0": "Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_1": "Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_2": "Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_3": "Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_4": "Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_5": "Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_6": "Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_7": "Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_8": "Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_9": "Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_10": "Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_11": "Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_12": "Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_13": "Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_14": "Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_15": "Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_16": "Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_17": "Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_18": "Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_19": "Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_20": "Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_21": "Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_22": "Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_23": "Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_24": "Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_25": "Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_26": "Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_27": "Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_28": "Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_29": "Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_30": "Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True", "layer_31": "Sterpus is amenable. Polly is amenable. True"}, {"prompt": "Wumpuses are moderate. Grimpus is wumpus. Stella is grimpus. True or false: Stella is moderate. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Wumpuses are moderate. Dumpus is lorpus. Stella is grimpus. True or false: Stella is moderate. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Stella is grimpus. Grimpus is wumpus. Stella is wumpus. Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_0": "Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_1": "Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_2": "Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_3": "Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_4": "Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_5": "Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_6": "Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_7": "Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_8": "Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_9": "Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_10": "Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_11": "Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_12": "Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_13": "Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_14": "Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_15": "Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_16": "Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_17": "Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_18": "Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_19": "Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_20": "Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_21": "Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_22": "Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_23": "Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_24": "Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_25": "Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_26": "Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_27": "Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_28": "Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_29": "Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_30": "Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True", "layer_31": "Wumpuses are moderate. Stella is moderate. True"}, {"prompt": "Zumpus is sweet. Dumpus is zumpus. Sam is dumpus. True or false: Sam is sweet. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Zumpus is sweet. Impus is jompus. Sam is dumpus. True or false: Sam is sweet. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Sam is dumpus. Dumpus is zumpus. Sam is zumpus. Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_0": "Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_1": "Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_2": "Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_3": "Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_4": "Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_5": "Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_6": "Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_7": "Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_8": "Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_9": "Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_10": "Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_11": "Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_12": "Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_13": "Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_14": "Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_15": "Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_16": "Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_17": "Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_18": "Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_19": "Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_20": "Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_21": "Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_22": "Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_23": "Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_24": "Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_25": "Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_26": "Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_27": "Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_28": "Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_29": "Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_30": "Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True", "layer_31": "Zumpus is sweet. Sam is sweet. True"}, {"prompt": "Impus is fast. Vumpuses are impuses. Alex is vumpus. True or false: Alex is fast. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Impus is fast. Brimpus is lorpus. Alex is vumpus. True or false: Alex is fast. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Alex is vumpus. Vumpuses are impuses. Alex is impus. Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True", "layer_0": "Alex is fast.", "layer_1": "Alex is fast. True", "layer_2": "Alex is fast. True", "layer_3": "Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True", "layer_4": "Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True", "layer_5": "Alex is fast. True", "layer_6": "Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True", "layer_7": "Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True", "layer_8": "Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True", "layer_9": "Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True", "layer_10": "Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True", "layer_11": "Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True", "layer_12": "Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True", "layer_13": "Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True", "layer_14": "Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True", "layer_15": "Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True", "layer_16": "Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True", "layer_17": "Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True", "layer_18": "Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True", "layer_19": "Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True", "layer_20": "Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True", "layer_21": "Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True", "layer_22": "Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True", "layer_23": "Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True", "layer_24": "Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True", "layer_25": "Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True", "layer_26": "Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True", "layer_27": "Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True", "layer_28": "Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True", "layer_29": "Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True", "layer_30": "Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True", "layer_31": "Impus is fast. Alex is fast. True"}, {"prompt": "Grimpuses are transparent. Jompuses are grimpuses. Max is jompus. True or false: Max is transparent. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Grimpuses are transparent. Wumpus is rompus. Max is jompus. True or false: Max is transparent. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Max is jompus. Jompuses are grimpuses. Max is grimpus. Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_0": "Impuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True.", "layer_1": "Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_2": "Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_3": "Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_4": "Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_5": "Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_6": "Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_7": "Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_8": "Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_9": "Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_10": "Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_11": "Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_12": "Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_13": "Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_14": "Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_15": "Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_16": "Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_17": "Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_18": "Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_19": "Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_20": "Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_21": "Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_22": "Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_23": "Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_24": "Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_25": "Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_26": "Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_27": "Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_28": "Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_29": "Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_30": "Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True", "layer_31": "Grimpuses are transparent. Max is transparent. True"}, {"prompt": "Vumpuses are dull. Jompuses are vumpuses. Sally is jompus. True or false: Sally is blue. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Vumpuses are dull. Brimpus is grimpus. Sally is jompus. True or false: Sally is blue. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Sally is jompus. Jompuses are vumpuses. Sally is vumpus. Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_0": "Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_1": "Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_2": "Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_3": "Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_4": "Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_5": "Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_6": "Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_7": "Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_8": "Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_9": "Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_10": "Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_11": "Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_12": "Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_13": "Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_14": "Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_15": "Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_16": "Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_17": "Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_18": "Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_19": "Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_20": "Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_21": "Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_22": "Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_23": "Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_24": "Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_25": "Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_26": "Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_27": "Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_28": "Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_29": "Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_30": "Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False", "layer_31": "Vumpuses are dull. Sally is dull. False"}, {"prompt": "Grimpuses are dull. Yumpuses are grimpuses. Alex is yumpus. True or false: Alex is dull. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Grimpuses are dull. Brimpus is lorpus. Alex is yumpus. True or false: Alex is dull. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Alex is yumpus. Yumpuses are grimpuses. Alex is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_0": "Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_1": "Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_2": "Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_3": "Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_4": "Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_5": "Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_6": "Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_7": "Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_8": "Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_9": "Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_10": "Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_11": "Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_12": "Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_13": "Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_14": "Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_15": "Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_16": "Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_17": "Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_18": "Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_19": "Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_20": "Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_21": "Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_22": "Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_23": "Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_24": "Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_25": "Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_26": "Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_27": "Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_28": "Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_29": "Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_30": "Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_31": "Grimpuses are dull. Alex is dull. True"}, {"prompt": "Grimpuses are small. Vumpuses are grimpuses. Fae is vumpus. True or false: Fae is small. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Grimpuses are small. Tumpus is gorpus. Fae is vumpus. True or false: Fae is small. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Fae is vumpus. Vumpuses are grimpuses. Fae is grimpus. Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_0": "Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_1": "Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_2": "Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_3": "Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_4": "Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_5": "Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_6": "Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_7": "Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_8": "Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_9": "Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_10": "Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_11": "Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_12": "Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_13": "Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_14": "Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_15": "Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_16": "Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_17": "Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_18": "Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_19": "Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_20": "Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_21": "Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_22": "Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_23": "Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_24": "Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_25": "Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_26": "Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_27": "Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_28": "Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_29": "Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_30": "Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True", "layer_31": "Grimpuses are small. Fae is small. True"}, {"prompt": "Gorpuses are dull. Tumpuses are gorpuses. Alex is tumpus. True or false: Alex is happy. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Gorpuses are dull. Lempus is sterpus. Alex is tumpus. True or false: Alex is happy. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Alex is tumpus. Tumpuses are gorpuses. Alex is gorpus. Gorpuses are dull. Alex is dull. False", "layer_0": "Alex is happy. True.", "layer_1": "Alex is happy. True", "layer_2": "Gorpuses are dull. Alex is dull. False", "layer_3": "Gorpus is dull. Alex is dull. False", "layer_4": "Gorpuses are dull. Alex is dull. False", "layer_5": "Alex is happy. True", "layer_6": "Gorpus is dull. Alex is dull. False", "layer_7": "Gorpuses are dull. Alex is dull. False", "layer_8": "Gorpuses are dull. Alex is dull. False", "layer_9": "Gorpuses are dull. Alex is dull. False", "layer_10": "Gorpuses are dull. Alex is dull. False", "layer_11": "Gorpuses are dull. Alex is dull. False", "layer_12": "Gorpuses are dull. Alex is dull. False", "layer_13": "Gorpuses are dull. Alex is dull. False", "layer_14": "Gorpuses are dull. Alex is dull. False", "layer_15": "Gorpuses are dull. Alex is dull. False", "layer_16": "Gorpuses are dull. Alex is dull. False", "layer_17": "Gorpuses are dull. Alex is dull. False", "layer_18": "Gorpuses are dull. Alex is dull. False", "layer_19": "Gorpuses are dull. Alex is dull. False", "layer_20": "Gorpuses are dull. Alex is dull. False", "layer_21": "Gorpuses are dull. Alex is dull. False", "layer_22": "Gorpuses are dull. Alex is dull. False", "layer_23": "Gorpuses are dull. Alex is dull. False", "layer_24": "Gorpuses are dull. Alex is dull. False", "layer_25": "Gorpuses are dull. Alex is dull. False", "layer_26": "Gorpuses are dull. Alex is dull. False", "layer_27": "Gorpuses are dull. Alex is dull. False", "layer_28": "Gorpuses are dull. Alex is dull. False", "layer_29": "Gorpuses are dull. Alex is dull. False", "layer_30": "Gorpuses are dull. Alex is dull. False", "layer_31": "Gorpuses are dull. Alex is dull. False"}, {"prompt": "Numpus is earthy. Dumpuses are numpuses. Alex is dumpus. True or false: Alex is earthy. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Numpus is earthy. Brimpus is zumpus. Alex is dumpus. True or false: Alex is earthy. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Alex is dumpus. Dumpuses are numpuses. Alex is numpus. Numpus is earthy. Alex is earthy. True", "layer_0": "Numpuses are earthy. Alex is earthy. True.", "layer_1": "Alex is numpus. True", "layer_2": "Alex is earthy. True", "layer_3": "Numpuses are earthy. Alex is earthy. True", "layer_4": "Numpus is earthy. Alex is earthy. True", "layer_5": "Alex is earthy. True", "layer_6": "Alex is earthy. True", "layer_7": "Numpus is earthy. Alex is earthy. True", "layer_8": "Numpus is earthy. Alex is earthy. True", "layer_9": "Numpus is earthy. Alex is earthy. True", "layer_10": "Alex is earthy. True", "layer_11": "Numpus is earthy. Alex is earthy. True", "layer_12": "Numpus is earthy. Alex is earthy. True", "layer_13": "Numpus is earthy. Alex is earthy. True", "layer_14": "Numpus is earthy. Alex is earthy. True", "layer_15": "Numpus is earthy. Alex is earthy. True", "layer_16": "Numpus is earthy. Alex is earthy. True", "layer_17": "Numpus is earthy. Alex is earthy. True", "layer_18": "Numpus is earthy. Alex is earthy. True", "layer_19": "Numpus is earthy. Alex is earthy. True", "layer_20": "Numpus is earthy. Alex is earthy. True", "layer_21": "Numpus is earthy. Alex is earthy. True", "layer_22": "Numpus is earthy. Alex is earthy. True", "layer_23": "Numpus is earthy. Alex is earthy. True", "layer_24": "Numpus is earthy. Alex is earthy. True", "layer_25": "Numpus is earthy. Alex is earthy. True", "layer_26": "Numpus is earthy. Alex is earthy. True", "layer_27": "Numpus is earthy. Alex is earthy. True", "layer_28": "Numpus is earthy. Alex is earthy. True", "layer_29": "Numpus is earthy. Alex is earthy. True", "layer_30": "Numpus is earthy. Alex is earthy. True", "layer_31": "Numpus is earthy. Alex is earthy. True"}, {"prompt": "Grimpus is earthy. Vumpus is grimpus. Wren is vumpus. True or false: Wren is earthy. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Grimpus is earthy. Gorpus is wumpus. Wren is vumpus. True or false: Wren is earthy. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Wren is vumpus. Vumpus is grimpus. Wren is grimpus. Grimpus is earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_0": "Impus is earthy. Wren is earthy. True.", "layer_1": "Wren is earthy. True", "layer_2": "Grimpus is earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_3": "Grimpus is earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_4": "Wren is earthy. True", "layer_5": "Wren is earthy. True", "layer_6": "Wren is earthy. True", "layer_7": "Grimpus is earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_8": "Grimpus is earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_9": "Grimpus is earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_10": "Wren is earthy. True", "layer_11": "Grimpus is earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_12": "Grimpus is earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_13": "Grimpus is earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_14": "Grimpus is earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_15": "Wren is earthy. True", "layer_16": "Grimpus is earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_17": "Grimpus is earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_18": "Grimpus is earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_19": "Grimpus is earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_20": "Grimpus is earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_21": "Grimpus is earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_22": "Grimpus is earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_23": "Grimpus is earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_24": "Grimpus is earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_25": "Grimpus is earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_26": "Grimpus is earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_27": "Grimpus is earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_28": "Grimpus is earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_29": "Grimpus is earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_30": "Grimpus is earthy. Wren is earthy. True", "layer_31": "Grimpus is earthy. Wren is earthy. True"}, {"prompt": "Vumpuses are fruity. Sterpus is vumpus. Max is sterpus. True or false: Max is fruity. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Vumpuses are fruity. Tumpus is gorpus. Max is sterpus. True or false: Max is fruity. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Max is sterpus. Sterpus is vumpus. Max is vumpus. Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_0": "Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity.", "layer_1": "Max is fruity. True", "layer_2": "Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_3": "Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_4": "Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_5": "Max is fruity. True", "layer_6": "Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_7": "Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_8": "Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_9": "Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_10": "Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_11": "Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_12": "Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_13": "Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_14": "Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_15": "Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_16": "Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_17": "Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_18": "Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_19": "Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_20": "Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_21": "Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_22": "Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_23": "Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_24": "Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_25": "Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_26": "Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_27": "Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_28": "Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_29": "Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_30": "Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True", "layer_31": "Vumpuses are fruity. Max is fruity. True"}, {"prompt": "Rompuses are brown. Lorpus is rompus. Sam is lorpus. True or false: Sam is brown. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Rompuses are brown. Yumpus is wumpus. Sam is lorpus. True or false: Sam is brown. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Sam is lorpus. Lorpus is rompus. Sam is rompus. Rompuses are brown. Sam is brown. True", "layer_0": "Rompus is brown. Sam is brown.", "layer_1": "Sam is brown. True", "layer_2": "Rompuses are brown. Sam is brown. True.", "layer_3": "Rompuses are brown. Sam is brown. True", "layer_4": "Rompus are brown. Sam is brown. True", "layer_5": "Sam is brown. True", "layer_6": "Rompus is brown. Sam is brown. True", "layer_7": "Rompus are brown. Sam is brown. True", "layer_8": "Rompuses are brown. Sam is brown. True", "layer_9": "Rompus are brown. Sam is brown. True", "layer_10": "Rompuses are brown. Sam is brown. True", "layer_11": "Rompuses are brown. Sam is brown. True", "layer_12": "Rompuses are brown. Sam is brown. True", "layer_13": "Rompuses are brown. Sam is brown. True", "layer_14": "Rompuses are brown. Sam is brown. True", "layer_15": "Rompuses are brown. Sam is brown. True", "layer_16": "Rompuses are brown. Sam is brown. True", "layer_17": "Rompuses are brown. Sam is brown. True", "layer_18": "Rompuses are brown. Sam is brown. True", "layer_19": "Rompuses are brown. Sam is brown. True", "layer_20": "Rompuses are brown. Sam is brown. True", "layer_21": "Rompuses are brown. Sam is brown. True", "layer_22": "Rompuses are brown. Sam is brown. True", "layer_23": "Rompuses are brown. Sam is brown. True", "layer_24": "Rompuses are brown. Sam is brown. True", "layer_25": "Rompuses are brown. Sam is brown. True", "layer_26": "Rompuses are brown. Sam is brown. True", "layer_27": "Rompuses are brown. Sam is brown. True", "layer_28": "Rompuses are brown. Sam is brown. True", "layer_29": "Rompuses are brown. Sam is brown. True", "layer_30": "Rompuses are brown. Sam is brown. True", "layer_31": "Rompuses are brown. Sam is brown. True"}, {"prompt": "Grimpuses are dull. Numpuses are grimpuses. Sam is numpus. True or false: Sam is dull. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Grimpuses are dull. Yumpus is zumpus. Sam is numpus. True or false: Sam is dull. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Sam is numpus. Numpuses are grimpuses. Sam is grimpus. Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_0": "Impuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_1": "Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_2": "Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_3": "Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_4": "Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_5": "Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_6": "Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_7": "Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_8": "Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_9": "Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_10": "Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_11": "Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_12": "Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_13": "Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_14": "Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_15": "Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_16": "Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_17": "Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_18": "Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_19": "Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_20": "Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_21": "Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_22": "Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_23": "Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_24": "Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_25": "Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_26": "Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_27": "Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_28": "Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_29": "Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_30": "Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True", "layer_31": "Grimpuses are dull. Sam is dull. True"}, {"prompt": "Jompuses are dull. Dumpuses are jompuses. Alex is dumpus. True or false: Alex is dull. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Jompuses are dull. Zumpus is gorpus. Alex is dumpus. True or false: Alex is dull. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Alex is dumpus. Dumpuses are jompuses. Alex is jompus. Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_0": "Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_1": "Alex is dull. True", "layer_2": "Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_3": "Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_4": "Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_5": "Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_6": "Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_7": "Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_8": "Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_9": "Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_10": "Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_11": "Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_12": "Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_13": "Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_14": "Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_15": "Alex is dull. True", "layer_16": "Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_17": "Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_18": "Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_19": "Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_20": "Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_21": "Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_22": "Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_23": "Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_24": "Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_25": "Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_26": "Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_27": "Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_28": "Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_29": "Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_30": "Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True", "layer_31": "Jompuses are dull. Alex is dull. True"}, {"prompt": "Yumpus is muffled. Impus is yumpus. Fae is impus. True or false: Fae is muffled. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Yumpus is muffled. Zumpus is sterpus. Fae is impus. True or false: Fae is muffled. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Fae is impus. Impus is yumpus. Fae is yumpus. Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_0": "Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_1": "Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_2": "Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_3": "Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_4": "Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_5": "Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_6": "Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_7": "Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_8": "Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_9": "Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_10": "Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_11": "Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_12": "Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_13": "Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_14": "Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_15": "Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_16": "Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_17": "Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_18": "Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_19": "Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_20": "Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_21": "Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_22": "Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_23": "Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_24": "Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_25": "Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_26": "Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_27": "Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_28": "Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_29": "Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_30": "Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True", "layer_31": "Yumpus is muffled. Fae is muffled. True"}, {"prompt": "Sterpuses are small. Gorpus is sterpus. Stella is gorpus. True or false: Stella is small. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Sterpuses are small. Yumpus is vumpus. Stella is gorpus. True or false: Stella is small. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Stella is gorpus. Gorpus is sterpus. Stella is sterpus. Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True", "layer_0": "Sterpuses are small. Stella is small.", "layer_1": "Stella is small. True", "layer_2": "Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True.", "layer_3": "Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True", "layer_4": "Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True", "layer_5": "Stella is small. False", "layer_6": "Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True", "layer_7": "Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True", "layer_8": "Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True", "layer_9": "Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True", "layer_10": "Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True", "layer_11": "Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True", "layer_12": "Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True", "layer_13": "Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True", "layer_14": "Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True", "layer_15": "Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True", "layer_16": "Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True", "layer_17": "Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True", "layer_18": "Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True", "layer_19": "Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True", "layer_20": "Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True", "layer_21": "Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True", "layer_22": "Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True", "layer_23": "Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True", "layer_24": "Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True", "layer_25": "Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True", "layer_26": "Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True", "layer_27": "Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True", "layer_28": "Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True", "layer_29": "Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True", "layer_30": "Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True", "layer_31": "Sterpuses are small. Stella is small. True"}, {"prompt": "Rompus is large. Impuses are rompuses. Alex is impus. True or false: Alex is large. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Rompus is large. Yumpus is sterpus. Alex is impus. True or false: Alex is large. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Alex is impus. Impuses are rompuses. Alex is rompus. Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_0": "Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_1": "Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_2": "Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_3": "Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_4": "Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_5": "Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_6": "Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_7": "Rompuses are large. Alex is large. True", "layer_8": "Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_9": "Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_10": "Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_11": "Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_12": "Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_13": "Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_14": "Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_15": "Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_16": "Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_17": "Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_18": "Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_19": "Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_20": "Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_21": "Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_22": "Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_23": "Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_24": "Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_25": "Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_26": "Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_27": "Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_28": "Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_29": "Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_30": "Rompus is large. Alex is large. True", "layer_31": "Rompus is large. Alex is large. True"}, {"prompt": "Rompuses are transparent. Impus is rompus. Stella is impus. True or false: Stella is transparent. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Rompuses are transparent. Wumpus is brimpus. Stella is impus. True or false: Stella is transparent. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Stella is impus. Impus is rompus. Stella is rompus. Rompuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True", "layer_0": "Rompus is transparent. Stella is transparent.", "layer_1": "Stella is transparent. True", "layer_2": "Rompuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True.", "layer_3": "Rompuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True", "layer_4": "Rompuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True", "layer_5": "Stella is transparent. False", "layer_6": "Rompus are transparent. Stella is transparent. True", "layer_7": "Rompus are transparent. Stella is transparent. True", "layer_8": "Rompuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True", "layer_9": "Rompuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True", "layer_10": "Rompuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True", "layer_11": "Rompuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True", "layer_12": "Rompuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True", "layer_13": "Rompuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True", "layer_14": "Rompuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True", "layer_15": "Rompuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True", "layer_16": "Rompuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True", "layer_17": "Rompuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True", "layer_18": "Rompuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True", "layer_19": "Rompuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True", "layer_20": "Rompuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True", "layer_21": "Rompuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True", "layer_22": "Rompuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True", "layer_23": "Rompuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True", "layer_24": "Rompuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True", "layer_25": "Rompuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True", "layer_26": "Rompuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True", "layer_27": "Rompuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True", "layer_28": "Rompuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True", "layer_29": "Rompuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True", "layer_30": "Rompuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True", "layer_31": "Rompuses are transparent. Stella is transparent. True"}, {"prompt": "Impus is transparent. Shumpuses are impuses. Rex is shumpus. True or false: Rex is transparent. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Impus is transparent. Dumpus is yumpus. Rex is shumpus. True or false: Rex is transparent. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are impuses. Rex is impus. Impus is transparent. Rex is transparent. True", "layer_0": "Rex is transparent.", "layer_1": "Rex is transparent. True", "layer_2": "Rex is transparent. True", "layer_3": "Impus is transparent. Rex is transparent. True", "layer_4": "Impus is transparent. Rex is transparent. True", "layer_5": "Rex is transparent. True", "layer_6": "Rex is transparent. True", "layer_7": "Impus is transparent. Rex is transparent. True", "layer_8": "Impus is transparent. Rex is transparent. True", "layer_9": "Rex is transparent. True", "layer_10": "Impus is transparent. Rex is transparent. True", "layer_11": "Impus is transparent. Rex is transparent. True", "layer_12": "Impus is transparent. Rex is transparent. True", "layer_13": "Impus is transparent. Rex is transparent. True", "layer_14": "Impus is transparent. Rex is transparent. True", "layer_15": "Impus is transparent. Rex is transparent. True", "layer_16": "Impus is transparent. Rex is transparent. True", "layer_17": "Impus is transparent. Rex is transparent. True", "layer_18": "Impus is transparent. Rex is transparent. True", "layer_19": "Impus is transparent. Rex is transparent. True", "layer_20": "Impus is transparent. Rex is transparent. True", "layer_21": "Impus is transparent. Rex is transparent. True", "layer_22": "Impus is transparent. Rex is transparent. True", "layer_23": "Impus is transparent. Rex is transparent. True", "layer_24": "Impus is transparent. Rex is transparent. True", "layer_25": "Impus is transparent. Rex is transparent. True", "layer_26": "Impus is transparent. Rex is transparent. True", "layer_27": "Impus is transparent. Rex is transparent. True", "layer_28": "Impus is transparent. Rex is transparent. True", "layer_29": "Impus is transparent. Rex is transparent. True", "layer_30": "Impus is transparent. Rex is transparent. True", "layer_31": "Impus is transparent. Rex is transparent. True"}, {"prompt": "Sterpuses are sweet. Grimpuses are sterpuses. Wren is grimpus. True or false: Wren is sweet. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Sterpuses are sweet. Tumpus is lempus. Wren is grimpus. True or false: Wren is sweet. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Wren is grimpus. Grimpuses are sterpuses. Wren is sterpus. Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_0": "Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_1": "Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_2": "Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_3": "Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_4": "Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_5": "Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_6": "Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_7": "Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_8": "Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_9": "Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_10": "Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_11": "Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_12": "Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_13": "Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_14": "Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_15": "Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_16": "Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_17": "Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_18": "Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_19": "Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_20": "Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_21": "Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_22": "Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_23": "Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_24": "Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_25": "Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_26": "Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_27": "Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_28": "Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_29": "Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_30": "Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True", "layer_31": "Sterpuses are sweet. Wren is sweet. True"}, {"prompt": "Shumpuses are floral. Numpuses are shumpuses. Rex is numpus. True or false: Rex is floral. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Shumpuses are floral. Jompus is zumpus. Rex is numpus. True or false: Rex is floral. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Rex is numpus. Numpuses are shumpuses. Rex is shumpus. Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_0": "Rex is floral. Rex is floral. True or false: Rex is floral.", "layer_1": "Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_2": "Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_3": "Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_4": "Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_5": "Rex is floral. True", "layer_6": "Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_7": "Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_8": "Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_9": "Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_10": "Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_11": "Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_12": "Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_13": "Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_14": "Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_15": "Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_16": "Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_17": "Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_18": "Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_19": "Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_20": "Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_21": "Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_22": "Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_23": "Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_24": "Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_25": "Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_26": "Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_27": "Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_28": "Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_29": "Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_30": "Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True", "layer_31": "Shumpuses are floral. Rex is floral. True"}, {"prompt": "Wumpuses are cold. Numpuses are wumpuses. Wren is numpus. True or false: Wren is cold. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Wumpuses are cold. Gorpus is sterpus. Wren is numpus. True or false: Wren is cold. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Wren is numpus. Numpuses are wumpuses. Wren is wumpus. Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_0": "Wren is cold. True.", "layer_1": "Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_2": "Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_3": "Wumpuses are cold. True", "layer_4": "Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_5": "Wumpuses are cold. True", "layer_6": "Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_7": "Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_8": "Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_9": "Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_10": "Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_11": "Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_12": "Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_13": "Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_14": "Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_15": "Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_16": "Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_17": "Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_18": "Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_19": "Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_20": "Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_21": "Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_22": "Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_23": "Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_24": "Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_25": "Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_26": "Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_27": "Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_28": "Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_29": "Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_30": "Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True", "layer_31": "Wumpuses are cold. Wren is cold. True"}, {"prompt": "Wumpuses are slow. Lorpus is wumpus. Alex is lorpus. True or false: Alex is slow. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Wumpuses are slow. Tumpus is sterpus. Alex is lorpus. True or false: Alex is slow. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Alex is lorpus. Lorpus is wumpus. Alex is wumpus. Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_0": "Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_1": "Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_2": "Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_3": "Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_4": "Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_5": "Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_6": "Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_7": "Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_8": "Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_9": "Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_10": "Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_11": "Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_12": "Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_13": "Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_14": "Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_15": "Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_16": "Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_17": "Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_18": "Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_19": "Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_20": "Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_21": "Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_22": "Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_23": "Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_24": "Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_25": "Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_26": "Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_27": "Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_28": "Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_29": "Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_30": "Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_31": "Wumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True"}, {"prompt": "Numpuses are sweet. Lempus is numpus. Alex is lempus. True or false: Alex is sweet. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Numpuses are sweet. Vumpus is shumpus. Alex is lempus. True or false: Alex is sweet. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Alex is lempus. Lempus is numpus. Alex is numpus. Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_0": "Alex is sweet.", "layer_1": "Alex is sweet. True", "layer_2": "Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_3": "Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_4": "Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_5": "Alex is sweet. True", "layer_6": "Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_7": "Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_8": "Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_9": "Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_10": "Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_11": "Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_12": "Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_13": "Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_14": "Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_15": "Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_16": "Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_17": "Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_18": "Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_19": "Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_20": "Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_21": "Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_22": "Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_23": "Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_24": "Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_25": "Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_26": "Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_27": "Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_28": "Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_29": "Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_30": "Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True", "layer_31": "Numpuses are sweet. Alex is sweet. True"}, {"prompt": "Yumpuses are slow. Grimpus is yumpus. Alex is grimpus. True or false: Alex is snowy. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Yumpuses are slow. Zumpus is tumpus. Alex is grimpus. True or false: Alex is snowy. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Alex is grimpus. Grimpus is yumpus. Alex is yumpus. Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. False", "layer_0": "Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_1": "Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_2": "Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_3": "Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_4": "Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_5": "Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_6": "Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_7": "Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_8": "Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_9": "Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_10": "Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_11": "Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_12": "Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_13": "Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_14": "Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_15": "Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_16": "Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_17": "Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_18": "Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_19": "Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_20": "Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_21": "Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_22": "Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_23": "Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_24": "Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_25": "Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_26": "Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_27": "Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_28": "Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_29": "Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_30": "Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True", "layer_31": "Yumpuses are slow. Alex is slow. True"}, {"prompt": "Tumpuses are bitter. Jompuses are tumpuses. Sally is jompus. True or false: Sally is liquid. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Tumpuses are bitter. Shumpus is sterpus. Sally is jompus. True or false: Sally is liquid. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Sally is jompus. Jompuses are tumpuses. Sally is tumpus. Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. False", "layer_0": "Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True.", "layer_1": "Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True", "layer_2": "Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True", "layer_3": "Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True", "layer_4": "Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True", "layer_5": "Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True", "layer_6": "Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True", "layer_7": "Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True", "layer_8": "Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. False", "layer_9": "Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True", "layer_10": "Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True", "layer_11": "Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True", "layer_12": "Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. False", "layer_13": "Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True", "layer_14": "Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True", "layer_15": "Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True", "layer_16": "Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True", "layer_17": "Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True", "layer_18": "Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True", "layer_19": "Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True", "layer_20": "Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True", "layer_21": "Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True", "layer_22": "Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True", "layer_23": "Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True", "layer_24": "Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True", "layer_25": "Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True", "layer_26": "Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True", "layer_27": "Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True", "layer_28": "Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True", "layer_29": "Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True", "layer_30": "Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True", "layer_31": "Tumpuses are bitter. Sally is bitter. True"}, {"prompt": "Lempuses are bitter. Vumpuses are lempuses. Sam is vumpus. True or false: Sam is bitter. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Lempuses are bitter. Zumpus is numpus. Sam is vumpus. True or false: Sam is bitter. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Sam is vumpus. Vumpuses are lempuses. Sam is lempus. Lempuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True", "layer_0": "Empuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True.", "layer_1": "Sam is bitter. True", "layer_2": "Sam is bitter. True", "layer_3": "Lempuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True", "layer_4": "Lempuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True", "layer_5": "Sam is bitter. True", "layer_6": "Sam is bitter. True", "layer_7": "Lempuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True", "layer_8": "Lempuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True", "layer_9": "Lempuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True", "layer_10": "Sam is bitter. True", "layer_11": "Lempuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True", "layer_12": "Lempuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True", "layer_13": "Lempuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True", "layer_14": "Lempuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True", "layer_15": "Lempuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True", "layer_16": "Lempuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True", "layer_17": "Lempuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True", "layer_18": "Lempuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True", "layer_19": "Lempuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True", "layer_20": "Lempuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True", "layer_21": "Lempuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True", "layer_22": "Lempuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True", "layer_23": "Lempuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True", "layer_24": "Lempuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True", "layer_25": "Lempuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True", "layer_26": "Lempuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True", "layer_27": "Lempuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True", "layer_28": "Lempuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True", "layer_29": "Lempuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True", "layer_30": "Lempuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True", "layer_31": "Lempuses are bitter. Sam is bitter. True"}, {"prompt": "Jompuses are slow. Vumpus is jompus. Polly is vumpus. True or false: Polly is slow. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Jompuses are slow. Brimpus is gorpus. Polly is vumpus. True or false: Polly is slow. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Polly is vumpus. Vumpus is jompus. Polly is jompus. Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_0": "Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_1": "Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_2": "Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_3": "Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_4": "Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_5": "Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_6": "Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_7": "Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_8": "Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_9": "Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_10": "Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_11": "Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_12": "Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_13": "Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_14": "Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_15": "Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_16": "Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_17": "Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_18": "Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_19": "Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_20": "Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_21": "Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_22": "Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_23": "Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_24": "Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_25": "Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_26": "Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_27": "Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_28": "Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_29": "Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_30": "Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True", "layer_31": "Jompuses are slow. Polly is slow. True"}, {"prompt": "Tumpus is cold. Lempuses are tumpuses. Alex is lempus. True or false: Alex is cold. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Tumpus is cold. Lorpus is dumpus. Alex is lempus. True or false: Alex is cold. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Alex is lempus. Lempuses are tumpuses. Alex is tumpus. Tumpus is cold. Alex is cold. True", "layer_0": "Tumpuses are cold. Alex is cold. True.", "layer_1": "True", "layer_2": "Tumpus is cold. Alex is cold. True", "layer_3": "Tumpuses are cold. Alex is cold. True", "layer_4": "Tumpus is cold. Alex is cold. True", "layer_5": "Tumpuses are cold. True", "layer_6": "Alex is cold. True", "layer_7": "Tumpus is cold. Alex is cold. True", "layer_8": "Tumpus is cold. Alex is cold. True", "layer_9": "Tumpus is cold. Alex is cold. True", "layer_10": "Tumpus is cold. Alex is cold. True", "layer_11": "Tumpus is cold. Alex is cold. True", "layer_12": "Tumpus is cold. Alex is cold. True", "layer_13": "Tumpus is cold. Alex is cold. True", "layer_14": "Tumpus is cold. Alex is cold. True", "layer_15": "Tumpus is cold. Alex is cold. True", "layer_16": "Tumpus is cold. Alex is cold. True", "layer_17": "Tumpus is cold. Alex is cold. True", "layer_18": "Tumpus is cold. Alex is cold. True", "layer_19": "Tumpus is cold. Alex is cold. True", "layer_20": "Tumpus is cold. Alex is cold. True", "layer_21": "Tumpus is cold. Alex is cold. True", "layer_22": "Tumpus is cold. Alex is cold. True", "layer_23": "Tumpus is cold. Alex is cold. True", "layer_24": "Tumpus is cold. Alex is cold. True", "layer_25": "Tumpus is cold. Alex is cold. True", "layer_26": "Tumpus is cold. Alex is cold. True", "layer_27": "Tumpus is cold. Alex is cold. True", "layer_28": "Tumpus is cold. Alex is cold. True", "layer_29": "Tumpus is cold. Alex is cold. True", "layer_30": "Tumpus is cold. Alex is cold. True", "layer_31": "Tumpus is cold. Alex is cold. True"}, {"prompt": "Gorpuses are luminous. Lorpus is gorpus. Fae is lorpus. True or false: Fae is luminous. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Gorpuses are luminous. Tumpus is zumpus. Fae is lorpus. True or false: Fae is luminous. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Fae is lorpus. Lorpus is gorpus. Fae is gorpus. Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_0": "Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_1": "Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_2": "Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_3": "Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_4": "Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_5": "Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_6": "Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_7": "Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_8": "Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_9": "Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_10": "Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_11": "Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_12": "Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_13": "Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_14": "Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_15": "Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_16": "Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_17": "Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_18": "Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_19": "Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_20": "Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_21": "Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_22": "Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_23": "Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_24": "Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_25": "Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_26": "Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_27": "Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_28": "Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_29": "Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_30": "Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True", "layer_31": "Gorpuses are luminous. Fae is luminous. True"}, {"prompt": "Lempus is hot. Rompuses are lempuses. Sam is rompus. True or false: Sam is hot. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Lempus is hot. Numpus is gorpus. Sam is rompus. True or false: Sam is hot. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Sam is rompus. Rompuses are lempuses. Sam is lempus. Lempus is hot. Sam is hot. True", "layer_0": "Sam is hot. True", "layer_1": "Sam is hot. True", "layer_2": "Sam is hot. True", "layer_3": "Sam is hot. True", "layer_4": "Sam is hot. True", "layer_5": "Lempus is hot. Sam is hot. True", "layer_6": "Lempus is hot. Sam is hot. True", "layer_7": "Lempus is hot. Sam is hot. True", "layer_8": "Lempus is hot. Sam is hot. True", "layer_9": "Lempus is hot. Sam is hot. True", "layer_10": "Lempus is hot. Sam is hot. True", "layer_11": "Sam is hot. True", "layer_12": "Sam is hot. True", "layer_13": "Sam is hot. True", "layer_14": "Lempus is hot. Sam is hot. True", "layer_15": "Lempus is hot. Sam is hot. True", "layer_16": "Sam is hot. True", "layer_17": "Lempus is hot. Sam is hot. True", "layer_18": "Sam is hot. True", "layer_19": "Sam is hot. True", "layer_20": "Sam is hot. True", "layer_21": "Sam is hot. True", "layer_22": "Lempus is hot. Sam is hot. True", "layer_23": "Lempus is hot. Sam is hot. True", "layer_24": "Sam is hot. True", "layer_25": "Sam is hot. True", "layer_26": "Lempus is hot. Sam is hot. True", "layer_27": "Sam is hot. True", "layer_28": "Lempus is hot. Sam is hot. True", "layer_29": "Sam is hot. True", "layer_30": "Sam is hot. True", "layer_31": "Sam is hot. True"}, {"prompt": "Lempuses are transparent. Vumpuses are lempuses. Sam is vumpus. True or false: Sam is transparent. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Lempuses are transparent. Rompus is brimpus. Sam is vumpus. True or false: Sam is transparent. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Sam is vumpus. Vumpuses are lempuses. Sam is lempus. Lempuses are transparent. Sam is transparent. True", "layer_0": "Empuses are transparent. Sam is transparent. True.", "layer_1": "Lempuses are transparent. Sam is transparent. True", "layer_2": "Lempuses are transparent. Sam is transparent. True", "layer_3": "Lempuses are transparent. Sam is transparent. True", "layer_4": "Lempuses are transparent. Sam is transparent. True", "layer_5": "Lempuses are transparent. Sam is transparent. True", "layer_6": "Lempuses are transparent. Sam is transparent. True", "layer_7": "Lempuses are transparent. Sam is transparent. True", "layer_8": "Lempuses are transparent. Sam is transparent. True", "layer_9": "Lempuses are transparent. Sam is transparent. True", "layer_10": "Lempuses are transparent. Sam is transparent. True", "layer_11": "Lempuses are transparent. Sam is transparent. True", "layer_12": "Lempuses are transparent. Sam is transparent. True", "layer_13": "Lempuses are transparent. Sam is transparent. True", "layer_14": "Lempuses are transparent. Sam is transparent. True", "layer_15": "Lempuses are transparent. Sam is transparent. True", "layer_16": "Lempuses are transparent. Sam is transparent. True", "layer_17": "Lempuses are transparent. Sam is transparent. True", "layer_18": "Lempuses are transparent. Sam is transparent. True", "layer_19": "Lempuses are transparent. Sam is transparent. True", "layer_20": "Lempuses are transparent. Sam is transparent. True", "layer_21": "Lempuses are transparent. Sam is transparent. True", "layer_22": "Lempuses are transparent. Sam is transparent. True", "layer_23": "Lempuses are transparent. Sam is transparent. True", "layer_24": "Lempuses are transparent. Sam is transparent. True", "layer_25": "Lempuses are transparent. Sam is transparent. True", "layer_26": "Lempuses are transparent. Sam is transparent. True", "layer_27": "Lempuses are transparent. Sam is transparent. True", "layer_28": "Lempuses are transparent. Sam is transparent. True", "layer_29": "Lempuses are transparent. Sam is transparent. True", "layer_30": "Lempuses are transparent. Sam is transparent. True", "layer_31": "Lempuses are transparent. Sam is transparent. True"}, {"prompt": "Impuses are dull. Brimpus is impus. Stella is brimpus. True or false: Stella is dull. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Impuses are dull. Vumpus is lempus. Stella is brimpus. True or false: Stella is dull. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Stella is brimpus. Brimpus is impus. Stella is impus. Impuses are dull. Stella is dull. True", "layer_0": "Impuses are dull. Stella is dull.", "layer_1": "Impuses are dull. Stella is dull. True", "layer_2": "Impuses are dull. Stella is dull. True", "layer_3": "Impuses are dull. Stella is dull. True", "layer_4": "Impuses are dull. Stella is dull. True", "layer_5": "Stella is dull. True", "layer_6": "Impuses are dull. Stella is dull. True", "layer_7": "Impuses are dull. Stella is dull. True", "layer_8": "Impuses are dull. Stella is dull. True", "layer_9": "Impuses are dull. Stella is dull. True", "layer_10": "Impuses are dull. Stella is dull. True", "layer_11": "Impuses are dull. Stella is dull. True", "layer_12": "Impuses are dull. Stella is dull. True", "layer_13": "Impuses are dull. Stella is dull. True", "layer_14": "Impuses are dull. Stella is dull. True", "layer_15": "Impuses are dull. Stella is dull. True", "layer_16": "Impuses are dull. Stella is dull. True", "layer_17": "Impuses are dull. Stella is dull. True", "layer_18": "Impuses are dull. Stella is dull. True", "layer_19": "Impuses are dull. Stella is dull. True", "layer_20": "Impuses are dull. Stella is dull. True", "layer_21": "Impuses are dull. Stella is dull. True", "layer_22": "Impuses are dull. Stella is dull. True", "layer_23": "Impuses are dull. Stella is dull. True", "layer_24": "Impuses are dull. Stella is dull. True", "layer_25": "Impuses are dull. Stella is dull. True", "layer_26": "Impuses are dull. Stella is dull. True", "layer_27": "Impuses are dull. Stella is dull. True", "layer_28": "Impuses are dull. Stella is dull. True", "layer_29": "Impuses are dull. Stella is dull. True", "layer_30": "Impuses are dull. Stella is dull. True", "layer_31": "Impuses are dull. Stella is dull. True"}, {"prompt": "Impus is fruity. Shumpus is impus. Polly is shumpus. True or false: Polly is fruity. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Impus is fruity. Lempus is zumpus. Polly is shumpus. True or false: Polly is fruity. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Polly is shumpus. Shumpus is impus. Polly is impus. Impus is fruity. Polly is fruity. True", "layer_0": "Impus is fruity. Polly is fruity. True", "layer_1": "Impus is fruity. Polly is fruity. True", "layer_2": "Impus is fruity. Polly is fruity. True", "layer_3": "Impus is fruity. Polly is fruity. True", "layer_4": "Impus is fruity. Polly is fruity. True", "layer_5": "Impus is fruity. Polly is fruity. True", "layer_6": "Impus is fruity. Polly is fruity. True", "layer_7": "Impus is fruity. Polly is fruity. True", "layer_8": "Impus is fruity. Polly is fruity. True", "layer_9": "Impus is fruity. Polly is fruity. True", "layer_10": "Impus is fruity. Polly is fruity. True", "layer_11": "Polly is fruity. True", "layer_12": "Polly is fruity. True", "layer_13": "Polly is fruity. True", "layer_14": "Impus is fruity. Polly is fruity. True", "layer_15": "Polly is fruity. True", "layer_16": "Impus is fruity. Polly is fruity. True", "layer_17": "Polly is fruity. True", "layer_18": "Impus is fruity. Polly is fruity. True", "layer_19": "Polly is fruity. True", "layer_20": "Polly is fruity. True", "layer_21": "Polly is fruity. True", "layer_22": "Polly is fruity. True", "layer_23": "Polly is fruity. True", "layer_24": "Polly is fruity. True", "layer_25": "Polly is fruity. True", "layer_26": "Polly is fruity. True", "layer_27": "Polly is fruity. True", "layer_28": "Polly is fruity. True", "layer_29": "Polly is fruity. True", "layer_30": "Polly is fruity. True", "layer_31": "Polly is fruity. True"}, {"prompt": "Dumpuses are overcast. Impus is dumpus. Sally is impus. True or false: Sally is overcast. Let us think step by step.", "noise_prompt": "Dumpuses are overcast. Rompus is zumpus. Sally is impus. True or false: Sally is overcast. Let us think step by step.", "answer": "Sally is impus. Impus is dumpus. Sally is dumpus. Dumpuses are overcast. Sally is overcast. True", "layer_0": "Dumpuses are overcast. Sally is overcast. True", "layer_1": "Dumpuses are overcast. Sally is overcast. True", "layer_2": "Dumpuses are overcast. Sally is overcast. True", "layer_3": "Dumpuses are overcast. Sally is overcast. True", "layer_4": "Dumpuses are overcast. Sally is overcast. True", "layer_5": "Dumpuses are overcast. Sally is overcast. True", "layer_6": "Dumpuses are overcast. Sally is overcast. True", "layer_7": "Dumpuses are overcast. Sally is overcast. True", "layer_8": "Dumpuses are overcast. Sally is overcast. True", "layer_9": "Dumpuses are overcast. Sally is overcast. True", "layer_10": "Dumpuses are overcast. Sally is overcast. True", "layer_11": "Dumpuses are overcast. Sally is overcast. True", "layer_12": "Dumpuses are overcast. Sally is overcast. True", "layer_13": "Dumpuses are overcast. Sally is overcast. True", "layer_14": "Dumpuses are overcast. Sally is overcast. True", "layer_15": "Dumpuses are overcast. Sally is overcast. True", "layer_16": "Dumpuses are overcast. Sally is overcast. True", "layer_17": "Dumpuses are overcast. Sally is overcast. True", "layer_18": "Dumpuses are overcast. Sally is overcast. True", "layer_19": "Dumpuses are overcast. Sally is overcast. True", "layer_20": "Dumpuses are overcast. Sally is overcast. True", "layer_21": "Dumpuses are overcast. Sally is overcast. True", "layer_22": "Dumpuses are overcast. Sally is overcast. True", "layer_23": "Dumpuses are overcast. Sally is overcast. True", "layer_24": "Dumpuses are overcast. Sally is overcast. True", "layer_25": "Dumpuses are overcast. Sally is overcast. True", "layer_26": "Dumpuses are overcast. Sally is overcast. True", "layer_27": "Dumpuses are overcast. Sally is overcast. True", "layer_28": "Dumpuses are overcast. Sally is overcast. True", "layer_29": "Dumpuses are overcast. Sally is overcast. True", "layer_30": "Dumpuses are overcast. Sally is overcast. True", "layer_31": "Dumpuses are overcast. Sally is overcast. True"}]